anyhow we don't have a lot of time to
waste so here's your racist stuff for
tonight overnight the national Chapter
of Sigma Alpha Epsilon shutting their
University of Oklahoma chapter after
this shocking video surfaced appearing
to Show members using a racist
chant racism doesn't exist anymore
Lar
why do you always have to focus race on
your show just
stop you
first what am I supposed to
do seriously right I'll stop talking
about race when people stop being
racist oh and quick note to people
capturing racism on their phones can you
please stop shooting vertical
videos I mean have you never heard of
aspect ratio side
screen I want to experience my hate in
169 not 25 all
right just saying but I got to give
credit where credits du the University
of Oklahoma took Swift action the
University of Oklahoma president David
Boren has expelled two students related
to the racist chant incident that's
right they also kicked the fraternity
off campus so don't worry you won't be
seeing any more of those Frat Boys until
they're your
congressman
right welcome to America everybody
that's how it
works well who's supervising these F
brats anyway I mean wasn't there an
adult present and overnight another
video is surfaced this one appears to
show the fraternity's 78-year-old hous
mother oh that's good a hous
mother finally the voice of gentle
reason what did this what did this
little angel have to
say
man Oklahoma what the's going on there
seriously shame on you lady you're a
frat house mother you should know
better you have no excuse in a written
statement Gilbo says she is heartbroken
by any racist portrayal she does not
tolerate any form of discrimination and
she was only singing along to a rap
song oh oh really racist grandma that's
a song well what song is
[Music]
that sorry Fatma my bad I guess you can
sing it but maybe not with so much
Glee anyhow to help uh give us some more
perspective on the SAE fraternity
cultures 19 90s Oklahoma frat guy dra
train uh thanks for joining us uh dra
train Larry please don't call me dra
train anymore I'm I'm an adult I work on
Wall Street you can call me Dennis all
right deep dick Dennis
boom up bro I think I'll just go with
Dennis dealer's Choice bro dealer's
Choice okay look now now uh I'm assuming
you saw the video of your SA Brothers
right I did I did and it was disgusting
I completely denounced it you cannot use
that word oh good so you totally agree
I'm with you couldn't agree more that
word is racist and offensive clearly the
song should have been there will never
be a black guy in it say there will
never be a black guy in it say wait wait
wait
wait uh I don't think you see the point
oh my God I'm so sorry what do you guys
go by now African-American well I got it
I got it let me try that one off for
size I totally get it there will never
an African ameran and I say don't never
be an African am and I say stop it know
what you're totally right the
African-American thing does not work it
totally screws up the Rhythm not that I
have to tell you that you know okay
look this is the issue here is not the
specific words it it's the sentiment
that you're excluding minorities dude
dude
dude dude maybe you don't understand
what a Fred is dude it's not about
excluding anybody it's about including
people who are exactly like
you that really doesn't make any sense
it's because you've never experienced
the bonding with your Bros bro low until
you get all of your friends together on
a chilly Easter Sunday and run across a
football field for six hours with your
thumb up each other's asses you'll never
really understand what Brotherhood is
about I have two brothers and I'm a
brother
I understand Brotherhood whatever dude
dra Train everybody enough of that hey
America follow the nightly show with
Larry Wilmore on Twitter but don't
follow me home I want followers but I
don't want followers that's stalking